<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rosary</string>

    <string name="cross_sign_long">Sign of Cross(Long Version)</string>
    <string name="cross_sign_long_prayer">By the sign of the cross deliver us from our enemies, you who are our God. \n\n ✝ In the name of the Father, \n ✝ and of the Son. \n ✝ and of the Holy Spirit. \n\n\n Amen</string>

    <string name="apostles_creed">Apostles Creed</string>
    <string name="apostles_creed_prayer">I believe in God, the FatherAlmighty, Creator of Heaven and earth; and in Jesus Christ, His only Son, Our Lord, Who was conceived by the Holy Spirit, born of the Virgin Mary, suffered under Pontius Pilate, was crucified, died, an was buried. He descended into Hell. The third day He arose again from the dead; He ascended into Heaven, sitteth at the right hand of God, the Father Almighty; from thence He shall come to judge the living and the dead. \n\nI believe in the Holy Spirit, the holy Catholic Church, the communion of saints, the forgiveness of sins, the resurrection of the body, and the life everlasting.\n\n\nAmen</string>

    <string name="our_father">Our Father</string>
    <string name="our_father_prayer">Our Father. Who art in heaven, hallowed be Thy name; Thy kingdom come; Thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven. \n\nGive us this day our daily bread; and forgive us our trespasses as we forgive those who trespass against us; and lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from evil.\n\n\nAmen</string>

    <string name="hail_mary">Hail Mary</string>
    <string name="hail_mary_prayer">Hail Mary, full of grace. The Lord is with thee. Blessed art thou amongst women, and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus. \n\nHoly Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners, now and at the hour of our death. \n\n\nAmen.</string>

    <string name="cross_sign_small">Sign of Cross(Small Version)</string>
    <string name="cross_sign_small_prayer">\n ✝ In the name of the Father, \n ✝ and of the Son. \n ✝ and of the Holy Spirit. \n\n\n Amen</string>

    <string name="o_my_jesus">O my Jesus</string>
    <string name="o_my_jesus_prayer">O my Jesus, forgive us of our sins. Save us from the fires oof hell. Lead all souls into heaven, especially those in most need of thy mercy. \n\n\nAmen.</string>

    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>

</resources>